Sometimes, I don't know who I am
Doubting myself again
Can't find a light in the dark
And I'm finding myself in the rain
Tryna get out of the pain
Know that I've come so far
I made a promise, I'll never run and hide
I'm getting stronger
A little longer
Now I finally found my wings
I let go of everything
Decided to follow my heart
And I finally able to breathe
Finally able to see
Just who I was born to be
I'm waking up in my dream
Oh, yeah, that fires in my eyes
No sleep, you keep them lullabies
Cross hearts I've been the one to ride
Vroom-vroom, I'll see you later, bye
I keep it a hundred, we one in a million, no billion
No kiddin', no ceiling, that's limitless
Stars in the sky, we infinite
Envisioned it, just how I pictured it
Here we are, all of the lights
Spotlight is blinding my eyes
Just breathe and live and let it die
Lift up my head, I'ma rise
Spread out my wings, I'm a fly, fly high
I'm getting stronger
A little longer
Now I finally found my wings
I let go of everything
Decided to follow my heart
And I finally able to breathe
Finally able to see
Just who I was born to be
I'm waking up in my dream